Guide to the The Patty Mucha Papers MSS.342
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Subject Files
  - Steinem, Gloria: MS Magazine, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Stella, Frank: Free Standing Murals at Leo Castelli [Advertisement], November 11 - December 16, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Stern, Jane + Michael, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Stevenson, Charles, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Strider, Marjorie, 1964 - 2003 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - SunDance Magazine, 1971 - 1973 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Swan, Simone, May 22, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Ting, Walasse, July 15, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Tirsch, Judy, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Torn, Rip, 1973 - 1979 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Torvle, Tony, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Tyler, Richard O., 1961, 1971, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Vanderbeek, Johanna: Correspondence, 1990 - 2001 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Vanderbeek, Johanna: Postcards, 1985 - 2008 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Von Born, Heidi, March 25, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Waldman, Anne, 1975, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Warhol, Andy: Clippings, Correspondence, 1975 - 1991 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Warhol, Andy: Fort Reno Florist Note [Signed], undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Warhol, Andy: Polaroid of Patty Mucha + Jay Craven [Signed], 1972 - 1973 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Wehrer, Anne, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Wesselman, Claire, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Whalen, Philip, October 27, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Wilcock, John, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Willard, Nancy, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Williams, Emmett, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Wylie, Andrew: "girl in bed smells fucked", undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Young, Le Monte + Marian Zazella, 1966, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Youngerman, Jack, June 28, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Youth International Party: Button [Design by Patty Mucha], 1972 (Box 5, Object ID: 342.2.0005)
  - Youth International Party: Claes' Rubber Stamp, undated (Box 5, Object ID: 342.2.0004)
  - Youth International Party: Correspondence, 1971 - 1972 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Zakri, undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Zaleski, John, June 15, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Zavetsky, Bill, November 30, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Zucker, Barbara, undated, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Series IV: Media
  Series IV: Media contains 16mm and Super 8mm footage, one complete film, related out-takes and soundtrack material, and assorted home movies. Material is organized by content and retains donor's original order at the box level.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - Fiddlers Contest - Picture Craftsbury, undated; ID: 342.0001 (Box 8, Media ID: 342.0001)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Gauge: Super 8mm
    Length: [400 ft.]
    Currently unavailable until duplication occurs.
  - Sync - OT (Fiddlers), undated; ID: 342.0002 (Box 8, Media ID: 342.0002)
    Length: [300 ft.]
  - Out takes (Fiddlers), undated; ID: 342.0003 (Box 8, Media ID: 342.0003)
    Length: [100 ft.]
  - Out takes (Fiddlers) / The Move, undated; ID: 342.0004 (Box 8, Media ID: 342.0004)
  - Cuts - OT (Fiddlers) / Experiments con..., undated; ID: 342.0005 (Box 8, Media ID: 342.0005)
    Length: [200 ft.]
  - OT (Fiddlers), undated; ID: 342.0006 (Box 8, Media ID: 342.0006)
  - OT - (Rev - Browne), undated; ID: 342.0007 (Box 8, Media ID: 342.0007)
  - Fiddlers, undated; ID: 342.0008 (Box 8, Media ID: 342.0008)
    Original format: 1/4 " Audio Reel
    Length: [380 ft.]
  - Music - I (Fiddlers), undated; ID: 342.0009 (Box 8, Media ID: 342.0009)
  - Voice - 2 (Fiddlers), undated; ID: 342.0010 (Box 8, Media ID: 342.0010)
  - Tape #1 - A (Fiddlers), undated; ID: 342.0011 (Box 8, Media ID: 342.0011)
  - Tape #1 - B (Fiddlers), undated; ID: 342.0012 (Box 8, Media ID: 342.0012)
  - Tape #2 - A + B (Fiddlers), undated; ID: 342.0013 (Box 8, Media ID: 342.0013)
    Length: [250 ft.]
  - Tape #3 - A - Tape 4 - A (Fiddlers), undated; ID: 342.0014 (Box 8, Media ID: 342.0014)
  - Jay, undated; ID: 342.0015 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0015)
    Gauge: 16mm
  - O.T. (Olga V.T.), undated; ID: 342.0016 (Box 9, 16mm film reels ID: 342.0016)
    This film is silent. Color correction has been performed on the access file to compensate for faded dye.
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 342.0017 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0017)
  - Prim, undated; ID: 342.0018 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0018)
    Length: [500 ft.]
  - Danville Fair - 77, undated; ID: 342.0019 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0019)
  - Golfing, undated; ID: 342.0020 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0020)
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 342.0021 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0021)
  - Patty's footage from international House, undated; ID: 342.0022 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0022)
  - Stuart Ploury, undated; ID: 342.0023 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0023)
  - Icycles, undated; ID: 342.0024 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0024)
  - Benefit Party (Craig), undated; ID: 342.0025 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0025)
  - Craig/ Charlie "Wood", undated; ID: 342.0026 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0026)
    Length: [120 ft.]
  - Game Un-Edited, undated; ID: 342.0027 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0027)
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 342.0028 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0028)
  - Buidling, undated; ID: 342.0029 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0029)
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 342.0030 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0030)
  - Jack Fiddlers, undated; ID: 342.0031 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0031)
    Original format: Full coat mag soundtrack with perforations
    Length: [20 ft.]
  - Beginning (r.g.), undated; ID: 342.0034 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0034)
  - Out 2 - B +C (Fiddlers), undated; ID: 342.0035 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0035)
    Length: [10 ft.]
  - Sound Pcs, undated; ID: 342.0036 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0036)
  - Banjoe (Fiddlers), undated; ID: 342.0038 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0038)
  - Out 2 - B (Fiddlers), undated; ID: 342.0032 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0032)
    Length: [5 ft.]
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 342.0033 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0033)
  - Banjoe (Fiddlers), undated; ID: 342.0037 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0037)
    Length: [50 ft.]
  - Kirst, undated; ID: 342.0039 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0039)
    Length: [1 ft.]
  - Rainy K, undated; ID: 342.0040 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0040)
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 342.0041 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0041)
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 342.0042 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0042)
  - Chez Bloom - Turn Back, undated; ID: 342.0043 (Box 9, Media ID: 342.0043)
  - London St snow sculpt, undated; ID: 342.0044 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0044)
  - London St snow- Dogs, undated; ID: 342.0045 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0045)
  - Tom's Cluilrer House, undated; ID: 342.0046 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0046)
  - Al Tai Chi, undated; ID: 342.0047 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0047)
  - Work day (stemp), undated; ID: 342.0048 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0048)
  - W+S workday, undated; ID: 342.0049 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0049)
  - Close up of (Jeff), undated; ID: 342.0050 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0050)
  - Wader Sees, work day - Every peudedler the words, undated; ID: 342.0051 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0051)
  - Game - Sam + Jim, undated; ID: 342.0052 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0052)
  - Sunflower at garden, undated; ID: 342.0053 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0053)
  - VT. Patty, undated; ID: 342.0054 (Box 10, Super 8mm film reel ID: 342.0054)
    This film is silent.
  - Game B/W, undated; ID: 342.0055 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0055)
  - India Patty, undated; ID: 342.0056 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0056)
  - India (Patty), Sound (works), undated; ID: 342.0057 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0057)
  - Susan Rutcand Patty, undated; ID: 342.0058 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0058)
  - Game? Patty, undated; ID: 342.0059 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0059)
  - Kittens Inside & Out, undated; ID: 342.0060 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0060)
  - Boddy and Kitten - INS, undated; ID: 342.0061 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0061)
  - Jay (Cravs), undated; ID: 342.0062 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0062)
  - Jay - Cherry Valley (NY), undated; ID: 342.0063 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0063)
  - Patty's weth blumps, undated; ID: 342.0064 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0064)
  - Patty (Owls + Hawock), undated; ID: 342.0065 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0065)
  - Patty L.I. Expressway, undated; ID: 342.0066 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0066)
  - Cats NY, undated; ID: 342.0067 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0067)
  - Out of Clae's window, undated; ID: 342.0068 (Box 10, Super 8mm film reel ID: 342.0068)
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 342.0069 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0069)
  - Kittens inside, undated; ID: 342.0070 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0070)
  - Blach leader, undated; ID: 342.0071 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0071)
  - Blach leader, undated; ID: 342.0072 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0072)
  - Mostly Blach leader, undated; ID: 342.0073 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0073)
  - Blach leader, undated; ID: 342.0074 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0074)
  - Not empty (fully exposed), undated; ID: 342.0075 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0075)
  - Klüver?, undated; ID: 342.0076 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0076)
  - G & E, undated; ID: 342.0077 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0077)
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 342.0078 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0078)
  - P, undated; ID: 342.0079 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0079)
  - Cars, undated; ID: 342.0080 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0080)
  - LUTZE, undated; ID: 342.0081 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0081)
  - Pam, undated; ID: 342.0082 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0082)
  - Notable, undated; ID: 342.0083 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0083)
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 342.0084 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0084)
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 342.0085 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0085)
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 342.0086 (Box 10, Media ID: 342.0086)
- OVERSIZE Series II: Manuscripts
  - "Children's Story Drafts Artwork", 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - "Complaint / Inquiry Letters: Birds Eye Division", April 25, May 5, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - "Night Fantasy" by Patricia Muschinski, The Milwaukee Journal Student Art Calendar, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - "Publicity: Writing / Music", 1978, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - "Strong Point," Green Mountain Trading Post, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- OVERSIZE Series III: Subject Files
  - "1. Rose is a rose is a rose is a rose" [Unidentified Art Print], undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Art Times: A Cultural and Creative Journal - Volume 8, Number 3, October 1991 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Brainard, Joe: St. Peter's Episcopal Church Art Auction [Poster], 1971 (Folder 3)
  - Craven, Jay: "Impresario in the Mountains," Vermonter Magazine, October 21, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - The Dance Center of Columbia College Chicago - Fall 2000 Newsletter (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - di Prima, Diane: Solstice Greeting, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Dupuy / Adorno / Klüver, Olga: Correspondence, 1975, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - [Edwards], Karen: Correspondence, August 10, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Fisher, Joel: Artworks, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Giorno, John: Posters, 1991 - 2000 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Hay, Deborah: Posters, 1984 - 1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Hell, Richard: Clippings, 1979, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Hell, Richard: Photograph of Richard Hell + Patty Mucha by Bevan Davies, circa 1970 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Hell, Richard: Television appearing with Leather Secrets, CBGB [Poster], April 14th [no year] (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Higgins, Dick: Correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Levine, Les: Giorno Poetry Systems Institute, Inc. "His Holiness Dudjom Rinpoche" [Poster], October 29, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Nauman, Bruce: "Body Pressure", 1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Oldenburg, Claes: Clippings, 1969, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Oldenburg, Claes: Sidney Janis Gallery [Poster], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Pizer, John: Correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Rauschenberg, Robert: Clippings, 1979, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Roos, Tonie: Correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Strider, Marjorie: The City University Graduate Center Mall [Poster], March 4 - April 3, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Yippie Portfolio, 1972 (Folder 6)
  - Youth International Party: Ten Days to Change the World, Miami Beach [Poster], July 10 - 14, August 20 - 24, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Youth International Party: Ten Days to Change the World [Poster by Claes Oldenburg], 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Z Press Broadside: "Almost Heaven" by Joe Brainard, MIchael Brownstein, Kenward Elmslie, and Anne Waldman [Poster], August 30, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Accretion 2012 - Series III: Subject Files
  Scope and Content
  Series III: Subject Files, from the 2012 Accretion, contains correspondence, postcards, and invitations received by Patty Mucha. They are arranged alphabetically.
  - Adorno, Olga - postcards, Undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Alvarez, Maria - postcards, 1969-1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Atkinson, Brendan - postcards, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Bickford, Ed - postcards, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Bradshaw, David - Art show announcement with personal greeting, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Brainard, Joe - postcards, 1972-1975 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Carroll, Paul - postcards, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Copp, Fletcher - postcards, Undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Craven, Jay - postcards, 1979-1984 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Dalton, David - emails, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Davis, Michele - postcards, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Dawson, Adele, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Denney, Alice - Christmas card with message, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Denney, Alice - postcards, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Dlugos, Tim - postcards, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Doganis, Kostas - postcards, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Eisenhauer, Letty Lou - postcards, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Elmslie, Kenward - invitation to WEB's and Snapshot, Undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Elmslie, Kenward - postcards, 1980's (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Fisher, Joel - postcards, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Ford, Charles Henri, 1968-1979 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Fransconi, Angela - postcards, 1970's (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Gelb, Gretchen - postcards, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Giorno, John - postcards, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Grinstein, Elyse and Stanley - postcards, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Hay, Deborah & Bradshaw, David - postcards, 1969-1978 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Hendricks, John - postcards, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Higgins, Dick - postcards, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Holt, Nancy - postcards, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Inventory of 2012 Accretion of the Patty Mucha Papers (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Inventory of postcards, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Irvine, Chippy - Christmas card with message, Undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Jarvis, Barbara - postcards, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Johns, Jasper - postcards, Undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Johnson, Ellen - postcards, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Johnson, Ray - postcards, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Kogelnik, Kiki - postcards, Undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Konig, Kasper - postcards, Undated (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Lennon, John & Ono, Yoko - postcards, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - [Lerner / Abrams?], Michael - postcards, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Levine, Les - postcards, 1973-1977 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Manayselli, George - postcards, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Matthews, Harry - postcards, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Mostly Mailings - postcards, 1968-1982 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Murphy, Chris - postcards, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Netzow, Charles - postcards, Undated (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Newspaper clipping - revies of Rafael Soyer's painting "Pedestrians", Undated (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Nodland, Jayne - postcards, Undated (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Ogden, Doug - postcards, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Oldenburg, Claes - correspondence and photo, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Oldenburg, Claes - Pace "Happening" invite, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Oldenburg, Lisa - postcards, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Östblum, Barbrö, 1973-1984 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Paxton, Steve - postcards, 1971-1977 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Perreault, John & Haber, Ira Joel - postcards, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Prince Rainer von Deitz of Hessen - postcards, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Rauschenberg - Gagosian Gallery invite, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Rivers, Clarice - postcards, Undated (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Rivers, Larry - postcards, Undated (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Rockburne, Dorothea - postcards, Undated (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Sanders, Ed - postcards, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Schneemann, Carolee - postcards, Undated (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Sheilds, Alan - postcards, Undated (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Steinem, Gloria (Ms. Mag) - postcards, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Strider, Marjorie - postcards, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Unknown and Miscellaneous - postcards, Undated (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Vanderbeek, Johanna - postcard, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Vermont Group Shows - invitations, 1993, 1999, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Waldman, Anne - postcards, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Williams, Emmett and Annie - postcards, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Wurlitzer, Rudy - postcards, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 71)
- Accretion 2012 - Series V: Photographs
  Series V: Photographs, from the 2012 Accretion, contains photographic prints, contact sheets, and negatives. There are several portraits of Patty Mucha. A large portion of this series is snapshots taken by Patty Mucha of friends and family.
  - Note by Patty Mucha about photographs, Undated (Binder A)
  - "A" Preg at Martha's Vineyard, Undated (Binder A)
  - "B" Sand Elephant, Martha's Vineyard, Undated (Binder A)
  - "C" Calcutta, Benares, Khajaraho, Undated (Binder A)
  - "D" Summer, Dan and Jack at home, Undated (Binder A)
  - "E" Konarah, Calcutta, Puri, Undated (Binder A)
  - "F" Cherry Valley, camping, Undated (Binder A)
  - "G" Goa, Puri, Margoa, Undated (Binder A)
  - "H" Sammy Dan, Jay, LaRouche, Stew in C.P., Undated (Binder A)
  - "I" Vermont in snow, Undated (Binder A)
  - "J" Jody and Julie in costume, Undated (Binder A)
  - "K" Welfleet Beach, Undated (Binder A)
  - "L" Swamp - Julie and Jody, Undated (Binder A)
  - "M" Overexposed [Frankie], Undated (Binder A)
  - "N" Double exposure at Kenward's, Undated (Binder A)
  - "O" Wide angle lens - various spots, Undated (Binder A)
  - "P" House and Jay at arrival on farm, Undated (Binder A)
  - "Johanna Van Der Beek, Karen Karnes, Shari Deemis, Moi" snapshots, Undated (Binder A)
  - "[Khiver] Kids - Maja, Kristian" snapshots, Undated (Binder A)
  - "Some faded pix of Kenward" - snapshots, Undated (Binder A)
  - "Alan Sheilds" - snapshots, Undated (Binder A)
  - Patty Mucha nudes - copies, Undated (Binder A)
  - Patty Mucha nudes - original, Undated (Binder A)
  - Richard W. Brown - photos for "See Vermont", Undated (Binder A)
  - Photos of Patty Much - Al Huang, Jay Craven, Undated (Binder A)
  - Pat and Richard [Hell] - photo by Bevan Davies (copy), 1970 (Binder A)
  - Note by Patty Mucha, Undated (Binder B)
  - Mexico "A", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "B", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "C", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "D", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "E", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "F", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "G", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "H", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "I", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "J", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "K", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "L", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "M", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "N", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "O", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "P", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "Q", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "R", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "S", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "T", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Mexico "U", 1976 (Binder B)
  - Paul's Party [Vermont], 1976 (Binder B)
  - Susan's Practice [SB], Undated (Binder B)
  - Brad G., Undated (Binder B)
  - Deidre's (no contact sheet), Undated (Binder B)
  - Mexico (no contact sheet), Undated (Binder B)
  - Unknown (no contact sheet), Undated (Binder B)
  - Patty Mucha - nude photos (copies), Unknown photographer, Undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Patty Mucha - nude photos, medium format negatives and contact sheets, unknown photographer, Undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Patty Mucha - nude photos, medium format negatives and contact sheets, unknown photographer, Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Patty Mucha - nude photos (original), unknown photographer, Undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Patty Mucha - Photos by Alex Greco, circa 1959 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Minox 8mm negatives (30 envelopes), Undated (Box 13)
- Series VI: 2017 Accretion
  This series has not been arranged by an archivist.
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of materials created and collected by artist Patty Mucha documenting her family, high school education and artistic growth, and her friendships with various 20th century American artists. Materials in this series include correspondence with gallerists and other artists, ephemera promoting openings and other artistic events, small press art and poetry publications, and materials documenting her personal life, including family photographs, awards won in high school, and artistic works created in Mucha's youth.
  - High School Materials, circa 1949-1954 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
  - Family Photographs, undated (Box 14, Folder 3, Box 22)
  - Journal, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence -- General, 1964-2016 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Claes Oldenburg, 2007-2015 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Montreal Mussedes Arts, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Richard Hell, 2013-2016 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Robert Haywood, 1995-2002 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Kalliopi, 2010-2012 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Chrissie Iles (Whitney Museum), 2009 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Robert Rauschenberg and Change Inc., 1992 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Rosa Esmen, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Milly Glimcher (Pace Gallery), 2010 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Dodie Kazanjian, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - George Manupelli, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Joel Fisher, 1999-2016 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Sid Sachs, 2004-2015 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Art and Poetry Publications, 1954-2008 (Box 15, Box 16, Box 17)
  - Photograph Binders, 1970-2016 (Box 18, Box 19)
  - William Copley Paper and Wood Hand-held Toy, 1940-1996 (Box 20)
  - Personal Scrapbook, 1954-2013 (Box 21)
- Series VII. 2023 Accretion, 1936-2022; 1.50 Linear Feet in 3 manuscript boxes
  This series consists of a manuscript for the memoir, "Threads"; transcribed journal entries for 1960, 1967, 1970, and 2012; photographs from childhood, teen, and adult years; photographs with friends and Claes Oldenburg; correspondence; writings; letters to Oldenburg during the last years of his life; Mucha artwork images and exhibit information; and Oldenburg exhibition publicity and loan information.
  - Photograph -- St. Helen's High School Graduates, 1949 (Box Shared Fales 042, Folder 3)
  - "Threads" Memoir Manuscript, 2022 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - Daily Journal Entries, 1960, 1967, 1970, 2012 (Box 23, Folder 3-6)
  - Photographs: Patty Childhood, Early Adulthood, Family Groups, Friends, 1937-2017 (Box 23, Folder 7-9)
  - Photographs by Charlie Moore of Patty, Claes Oldenburg, Sculptures, 1964-1967 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Niki de Saint Phalle Movie Stills with Patty, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Images of Art with Patty as Subject, 1959, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Songs and Music by Mucha, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Mucha Early Writings and High School Design Work, 1951, 1963, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - "Sacred Geometry" Notebook and Journal, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Name Change Documents, Press Clippings, Letters, 1955-2015 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Chapbook, Love Chops, circa 2022 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Claes Oldenburg -- Exhibition Promotion, Photographs, Press Clippings, 1990-2021 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Hell, Richard, 1969-1980s (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Peace Prints Project -- Patty Mucha and Julie Martin, 2011-2022 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Exhibition -- Party for Övyind, 2019-2022 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Oldenburg Exhibition -- The 60's -- Invitation Cards, Loan Forms, 2011-2013 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Oldenburg, Richard and Mel, 1999-2022 (Box 24, Folder 14)